Google.chech.
Google.check。
for now. Let's turn our attention to
目前。 让我们把注意力转向
glasses. As you know, we've been
眼镜。 如您所知，我们
building glasses for over 10 years, and
生产眼镜已有十余年，从未
we've never stopped.
停止过。
Glasses with Android XR are lightweight
搭载 Android XR 系统的眼镜轻巧便携，
and designed for all day wear, even
即使内置多种科技，也适合全天佩戴
technology. A camera and microphones
。
give Gemini the ability to see and hear
双子座号利用摄像头和麦克风来观察和聆听
the world. Speakers let you listen to
世界。 扬声器可让您聆听
the AI, play music, or take calls. And
人工智能指令、播放音乐或接听电话。
an optional in lens display privately
镜头内置显示屏（可选）可在您需要时私密地
shows you helpful information just when
显示有用信息
you need it.
。
These glasses work with your phone,
这款眼镜可以与你的手机配合使用，
giving you access to your apps while
让你在解放双手的同时访问你的应用程序
keeping your hands free. All this makes
。 所有这些都使得
glasses a natural form factor for AI,
眼镜成为人工智能的天然形态，
bringing the power of Gemini right to
将 Gemini 的强大功能带到
where you are. So unlike Clark Kent, you
你身边。 所以，不像克拉克·肯特那样，
can get superpowers when you put your
戴上眼镜你就能获得超能力
on. Okay, who's up for seeing an early
。 好，谁想看看
demo of Android XR glasses?
Android XR 眼镜的早期演示？
Let's see how they work in the most
让我们看看他们在IO后台这种最繁忙的环境下是如何工作的
backstage at IO. Our very own superwoman
。 我们自己的女超人
Nisha is back there to show us how these
妮莎又回来了，她将向我们展示这些
glasses work for real. Let me send her a
眼镜的实际使用效果。 我现在就给她发条
text now and let's get started.
短信，我们开始吧。
Hey everyone. Right now, you should be
大家好。 现在，你应该能透过
the lens of my Android XR glasses. Like
我的 Android XR 眼镜的镜头看到和我一样的景象。 就像
my delicious coffee over here and that
我这杯美味的咖啡，还有
text from Sham that just came in. Let's
Sham刚刚发来的短信。
see what he
看看他
said. All right, it's definitely
说了什么。 好了，
showtime. So, I'm going to launch Gemini
演出时间到了。 所以，我要启动双子座计划，
and get us
让我们开始
going. Send a text that I'm getting
行动。 请发短信告诉我我即将
started and silence my notifications,
开始，并关闭我的通知
please.
。
Okay, I've sent that message to him and
好的，我已经把那条消息发给他了，并且
muted all your notifications.
关闭了你所有的通知。
Perfect.
完美的。
Oh, hey, Misha. Hey, deer. I see the
哦，嗨，米沙。 嘿，鹿。 我看到
lights on on your glasses, so I think
你眼镜上的灯亮着，所以我觉得可以
it's safe to say that we're live right
肯定地说，我们现在正在直播
now. Yes, we're officially on with the
。 是的，我们正式加入
IO crew. Hey, everybody. It is pretty
IO团队了。 大家好。
great to see IO from this angle. Nisha,
从这个角度看IO真是太棒了。 妮莎，
you promised me I could get my own pair
你答应过我，如果我在这里帮忙，就可以给我一副属于我自己的
of Android XR glasses if I helped out
安卓 XR 眼镜
back here. So, uh, what do you say? Of
。 所以，呃，你觉得怎么样？
course. Let's get coffee after this and
当然。 之后我们去喝咖啡吧，
I'll bring you those glasses. Awesome.
我去给你拿那些杯子。 惊人的。   到时候
We'll see you then. Good luck. Thank
见。 祝你好运。
you. As you all can see, there's a ton
谢谢。 正如大家所见，
going on backstage. And is that pro
后台非常热闹。 那位
basketball player Giannis wearing our
戴着我们眼镜的职业篮球运动员扬尼斯·阿德托昆博吗
glasses? I love them. This place both of
？ 我喜欢它们。 把
my hands for double high fives.
双手放在这里，准备和大家击掌。
Nice. Let me keep showing you guys what
好的。 让我继续向大家展示
these glasses can do. I've been curious
这款眼镜的功能。 我一整天都
about this photo wall all day. Like,
对这面照片墙很好奇。
what band is this? And how are they
这是哪个乐队？ 它们
connected to this place?
与这个地方有什么联系？
at Shoreline Amphitheater, which are
在海岸线露天剧场，这
often seen as homecoming shows for the
通常被视为乐队的返乡演出
band. No way. Can you show me a photo of
。 决不。 你能给我看看
one of their performances here?
他们在这里演出的照片吗？
Sure. Here's one. Want me to play one of
当然。 这里有一个例子。 想让我播放
their songs? I'd love that. I can listen
他们的一首歌吗？ 我非常乐意。 我可以一边听一边走向
while I make my way to the stage.
舞台。
Right. Here's Under the Aurora by
正确的。 这是 Counting Crows 的《Under the Aurora》
Counting Crows.
。
Okay, who's ready to see these buses?
好了，谁准备好去看这些巴士了？
[Applause]
[掌声]
Welcome, mister. Hey, everyone.
欢迎，先生。 大家好。
Thanks for that star studded behind the
感谢你带我们一窥星光熠熠的
scenes look. By the way, do you want to
幕后花絮。 对了，你
book that coffee with Dita now? Yes. The
现在想和迪塔约咖啡吗？ 是的。
crew actually gave me some awesome
工作人员在后台给了我一些很棒的
coffee backstage. So, let me try
咖啡。 那么，让我尝试
something fun.
一些有趣的事情。
Gemini, what was the name of the coffee
双子座，
shop on the cup I had earlier?
我之前喝的那杯咖啡店叫什么名字？
H, that might have been Bloom's giving.
哦，那可能是布鲁姆的捐赠。
From what I can tell, it's a vibrant
据我观察，这是一家
coffee shop on Castro Street. Great
位于卡斯特罗街的充满活力的咖啡馆。 美好的
memory.
回忆。
Can you show me the photos of that cafe?
你能给我看看那家咖啡馆的照片吗？
I want to check out the vibes.
我想感受一下氛围。
Definitely. Do these photos from maps
确实。 这些地图上的照片有
help? Oh, I know that spot. It's a
帮助吗？ 哦，我知道那个地方。 它既是
flower shop as well as a coffee shop,
花店又是咖啡店，
but it is downtown. H Okay, Gemini, show
而且位于市中心。 好的，双子座，告诉
me what it would take to walk here.
我走到这里需要付出什么代价。
Getting those directions now. It'll take
现在正在获取路线信息。
you about an hour.
大约需要一个小时。
Okay, I can get some steps in. And these
好的，我可以走几步。有了这些
heads up directions and a full 3D map
提示和完整的3D地图，
should make it super easy.
应该会变得非常简单。
[Applause]
[掌声]
Go ahead and send deer an invite for
去吧，给鹿群发个
that cafe and get coffee at 3 p.m.
咖啡馆的邀请函，下午三点一起去喝咖啡。
today.
今天。
I'll send out that invite now. Enjoy the
我现在就发出邀请。 请享用
coffee.
咖啡。
As you saw, Gemini helped Nisha search
正如你所看到的，Gemini 帮助 Nisha 搜索
what she sees, remember details like the
她看到的东西，记住咖啡杯之类的细节
coffee coffee cup, book an event, even
，预订活动，甚至
navigate, all without taking her phone
导航，所有这些都无需她把手机
out of her pocket. I'm even wearing the
从口袋里拿出来。 我
glasses right now, too. They're my
现在就戴着这副眼镜呢。 它们就是我的
They're my personal teleprompter, and I
私人提词器，而且我
have prescription lenses, so I can see
戴着近视眼镜，所以我能看到
you all. Okay, Nisha, this is a big
你们所有人。 好了，妮莎，这
moment for glasses. Let's capture it.
对眼镜来说是个重要时刻。 我们把它拍下来。   是的
Yes. Get ready for a quick photo,
。 大家准备好快速拍张照片
everyone. And let's bring out our star.
。 让我们请出我们的明星。
Take on theme.
围绕主题展开。
All right, Gemini. Janice, take a photo
好的，双子座。 珍妮丝，帮我拍张照片
for me.
。
All right, Gemini, take a photo for me
好的，双子座，帮我拍张照片，
and add it to my favorites.
然后添加到我的收藏夹里。
That looks
看起来棒
amazing. I'm completely starruck. Okay,
极了！（掌声） 我完全崩溃了。 好的，
one last thing. Sunda showed what's
最后一件事。  Sunda 此前展示了
possible with live chat translation
实时聊天翻译的可能性
earlier. Let's see what that's like on
。 我们来看看戴眼镜是什么感觉
glasses. This is a very risky demo, but
。 这是一个风险很大的演示，但
we're going to give it a
我们决定
shot. Nisha and I are going to speak to
试一试。 妮莎和我将用
each other in our mother tongues. Nisha
各自的母语交谈。 妮莎
is going to speak Hindi. I'm going to
要讲印地语。 我接下来
speak FYI very poorly. And you'll see
要说的可能不太好听。 您可以在这里看到
the feed from both of our glasses back
我们两个眼镜的画面
here. And so you can all follow along,
。 为了方便大家跟上，
we'll show an English translation in
我们将实时显示英文翻译
real time. Okay, let's give it a shot.
。 好吧，我们试试看。
Fingers crossed.
但愿如此。
Huh? Bill.
嗯？ 账单。
man. See, we said it's a risky
男人。 你看，我们说过这是一个有风险的
demo.
演示。
you. Thank you so much.
谢谢。 太感谢了。
Thank you, Nester, for that awesome tour
感谢 Nester 为大家带来的精彩
of Android XR
Android XR
glasses. We're so excited about the
眼镜体验之旅。 我们对
side with these Android XR devices. But
Android XR 设备带来的各种可能性感到无比兴奋，因为有了这些设备，您身边就会有非常实用的 AI 助手。 但这
that's not all. We're taking our
还不是全部。 我们将
partnership with Samsung to the next
与三星的合作提升到一个新的
level by extending Android XR beyond
水平，把 Android XR 技术从
headsets to
头戴式设备扩展到
glasses. We're creating the software and
眼镜领域。 我们正在创建软件和
reference hardware platform to enable
参考硬件平台，以使
the ecosystem to build great glasses
生态系统能够与我们一起打造出色的眼镜
alongside us.
。
Web Pokemon
网络宝可梦
Blue Iron O.
蓝色铁O。
Hello everyone. Good morning. Welcome to
大家好。 早上好。 欢迎来到
Google
Google
IO. So good to see everyone here in
I/O。 很高兴在肖尔莱恩见到大家，
Shoreline and hello to everyone joining
也向世界各地通过网络参与的朋友们问好
virtually around the world. I learned
。 我了解到
that today is the start of Gemini
今天是双子座的开始
season. I'm not really sure what the big
。 我不太明白这有什么
deal is. Every day is Gemini season here
大不了的。
at
在
Google. Normally, you wouldn't have
谷歌，每天都是双子座的季节。 通常情况下，
heard much from us in the weeks leading
在 IO 大会之前的几周里，你们不会听到我们太多消息
up to IO. That's because we'd be saving
。 那是因为我们会把
our best models for this stage. But in
最好的模型留到这个阶段使用。 但在
our Gemini era, we just as likely to
我们的 Gemini 时代，我们同样有可能
ship our most intelligent model on a
在三月份一个普通的星期二发布我们最智能的型号，
random Tuesday in March or a really cool
或者在发布前
breakthrough like Alpha Evolve just a
一周推出像 Alpha Evolve 这样非常酷的突破
week before. We want to get our best
。 我们希望尽快将我们最好的
models into your hands and our products
模型和产品送到您手中
ASAP. And so we are shipping faster than
。 因此，我们的发货速度比以往任何时候都快
ever. We have announced over a dozen
。 自上次 I/O 大会以来，我们已经发布了十几个
models and research breakthroughs and
模型和研究突破，并
released over 20 major AI products and
推出了 20 多个重要的 AI 产品和
features all since the last IO. I'm
功能。 我
particularly excited about the rapid
对模型的快速进展感到特别兴奋
model progress. You can see the step
。 您可以在这里看到阶跃
function change here. ELO scores, one
函数的变化。  ELO 分数是
measure of progress, are up more than
衡量进步的指标之一，
300 points since the first generation of
自第一代 Gemini Pro 发布以来，分数提高了 300 多分
Gemini Pro. And today, Gemini 2.5 Pro
。 今天，Gemini 2.5 Pro
sweeps the Elm Marina leaderboard in all
横扫 Elm Marina 排行榜所有
categories. It is state-of-the-art on
类别。 它在
many, many benchmarks. And we've also
许多方面都达到了最先进的水平。 我们
made rapid progress in coding. Our
在编程方面也取得了快速进展。 我们
updated 2.5 Pro reached number one on
更新后的 2.5 Pro 版本在
webdev arena and now surpasses the
webdev 领域排名第一，现在比
previous version by 142 ELO points. It's
之前的版本高出 142 个 ELO 积分。 感谢大家，它在各大
getting a lot of love across the top
主流编程平台上都获得了很高的评价
coding platforms thanks to all of you.
。   在
On cursor, the leading AI code editor,
领先的 AI 代码编辑器 Cursur 上，
Gemini is the fastest growing model of
Gemini 是今年增长最快的型号
the year, producing hundreds of
，每分钟都能生成数
thousands of lines of accepted code
十万行被接受的代码
every single minute.
。
Now, this last milestone might be the
现在，这最后一个里程碑或许是
most impressive, at least in some
最令人印象深刻的，至少在某些
circles. A couple of weeks ago, Gemini
圈子里是这样。 几周前，Gemini
completed Pokemon
完成了《精灵宝可梦：
Blue. It earned all eight badges,
蓝》。 它获得了全部八枚徽章，
traveled the victory road, defeated the
走过了胜利之路，击败了
Elite 4, and the champion, bringing us
四天王和冠军，使我们
one step closer to achieving API,
离实现 API（人工智能宝可梦）又近了一步
artificial Pokemon intelligence.
。
All of this progress is enabled by our
所有这些进展都得益于我们
worldleading infrastructure, the
世界领先的基础设施，这是
foundation of our full stack approach to
我们全栈式人工智能方法的基础
AI. Our seventh generation TPU,
。 我们的第七代 TPU，
Ironwood, is the first design to power
Ironwood，是首款能够
thinking and inference at scale. It
大规模驱动思维和推理的设计。 它
delivers 10x the performance over the
比上一代产品性能提升了 10 倍
previous generation and packs an
，
incredible 42.5 exaflops of compute per
每个部件的计算能力高达 42.5 exaflops
part. Just amazing. and it's coming to
。 简直太棒了。 这项服务将于
Google Cloud customers later this
今年晚些时候面向谷歌云客户推出
year. Our infrastructure strength down
。 我们强大的基础设施，包括
to the TPU is what helps us deliver
TPU，使我们能够交付速度
dramatically faster models. Of the top
大幅提升的模型。 在
models on the LM Marina leaderboard,
LM Marina 排行榜的顶级模型中，
Gemini holds the top three spots for
Gemini 占据了
highest output tokens generated per
每秒生成代币数量最多的前三名
second. All while model prices are
。 与此同时，车型价格却
coming down significantly.
大幅下降。
There's a hard trade-off between price
价格和性能之间存在着难以取舍的取舍
and performance. Yet over and over,
。 然而，我们一次又一次地
models at the most effective price
以最优惠的价格提供了最好的产品
point. Not only is Google leading this
。 谷歌不仅引领着这场
parade of Frontier, we've fundamentally
前沿科技的潮流，而且从根本上
shifted the frontier itself. The result,
改变了前沿科技本身。 其结果是，世界
everywhere. And the world is responding
各地的人们都能获得更多智能。 世界正在以前所未有的
and adopting AI faster than ever
速度响应并采用人工智能
before. It's one marker of progress.
。 这是进步的标志之一。
This time last year, we were processing
去年这个时候，我们
9.7 trillion tokens a month across our
每月通过我们的产品和 API 处理 9.7 万亿个代币
products and APIs. Now, we are
。 现在，我们
processing 480 trillion monthly tokens.
每月处理 480 万亿个代币。
That's about a 50x increase in just a
这相当于一年内增长了约 50 倍
year. We're also seeing a wave of
。 我们还看到，
adoption across our developer AI tools.
我们的开发者人工智能工具正在迎来一波普及浪潮。
Today, over 7 million developers have
如今，已有超过 700 万开发者在
Google AI Studio and Vert.ex AI. Over 5x
Google AI Studio 和 Vert.ex AI 中使用 Gemini API 进行开发。
growth since last IO and Gemini usage on
自上次 I/O 以来增长超过 5 倍，Vertex AI 上的 Gemini 使用量
Vertex AI is up more than 40 times since
自去年以来增长超过 40 倍
last year. AI adoption is increasing
。 人工智能
across our products. The Gemini app now
在我们产品中的应用越来越广泛。  Gemini 应用目前
has over 400 million monthly active
拥有超过 4 亿月活跃
users. We are seeing strong growth and
用户。 我们看到，
engagement particularly with 2.5 models.
2.5 型号的车型尤其实现了强劲的增长和用户参与度。
For those using 2.5 Pro in the Gemini
对于在 Gemini 应用中使用 2.5 Pro 的用户来说
app, usage has gone up
，使用率上升了
45%. You will hear a lot more about the
45%。 稍后您会听到更多关于
Gemini app later. We're also seeing
Gemini 应用的信息。 我们还看到，
incredible momentum in search today. AI
如今搜索领域也呈现出强劲的发展势头。  AI
overviews have more than 1.5 billion
概览网站每月拥有超过15亿
users every month. That means Google
用户。 这意味着谷歌
search is bringing generative AI to more
搜索比世界上任何其他产品都更能惠及更多的人，让更多人体验到生成式人工智能
world. And along with AI overviews, AI
。 除了 AI 概览之外，AI
mode is the next big step for search.
模式是搜索的下一个重大进步。
later. What all this progress means is
稍后你会听到更多相关消息。 所有这些进展意味着
that we are in a new phase of the AI
我们正处于人工智能
platform shift where decades of research
平台转型的新阶段，数十年的研究成果
are becoming reality for people all over
正在成为世界各地人们的现实
the world.
。
Foreign speech. Foreign speech. Foreign
外语。 外语。
speech.
外语。
Fore flash.
前闪光。
Fore USA leave
美国政府应该
code deep
深入
think. Thanks Tulsi. We've been busy
思考，并制定相关法规。 谢谢图尔西。 我们一直在忙着
exploring the frontiers of thinking
探索
capabilities in Gemini
Gemini
2.5. As we know from our experience with
2.5 的思维能力的边界。 我们从
Alph Go, responses improve when we give
Alpha Go 的经验中得知，当我们给
these models more time to
这些模型更多
think. Today, we're making 2.5 Pro even
思考时间时，它们的响应速度会提高。 今天，我们将
better by introducing a new mode we're
通过引入一种
calling Deep
名为“深度
Think. It pushes model performance to
思考”的新模式，使 2.5 Pro 变得更好。 它将模型性能发挥到
its limits, delivering groundbreaking
极致，取得了突破性
results. Deepthink uses our latest
成果。  Deepthink 运用了我们
cutting edge research in thinking and
在思维和推理方面的最新前沿研究成果
reasoning, including parallel
，包括并行
techniques. So far, we've seen
技术。 到目前为止，我们已经看到了
incredible performance. It gets an
令人难以置信的表现。 它
impressive score on USA Mo 2025,
在 USA Mo 2025 上获得了令人印象深刻的分数，这是
currently one of the hardest mass
目前最难的质量
benchmarks. It leads on live codebench,
基准测试之一。 它在实时代码基准测试中领先，这是
a difficult benchmark for co competition
一个针对竞技级编程的困难基准测试
level coding. And since Gemini has been
。 由于 Gemini
natively multimodal from the start, it's
从一开始就是原生多模态的，因此
no surprise that it also excels on the
它在衡量 MMU 的主要基准测试中表现出色也就不足为奇了
MMU. Because we're defining the frontier
。 因为我们正在
with 2.5 Pro Deep Think, we're taking a
用 2.5 Pro Deep Think 定义前沿，所以我们花了
little bit of extra time to conduct more
一些额外的时间来进行更多的
Frontier safety evaluations and get
前沿安全评估，并
further input from safety experts. As
从安全专家那里获得更多意见。 作为
part of that, we're going to make it
其中的一部分，我们将
available to trusted testers via the
通过 Gemini API 将其提供给受信任的测试人员，
Gemini API to get their feedback before
以便在广泛发布之前获得他们的反馈
making it widely available. You'll hear
。 今天晚些时候，Josh 会
more about our plans for 2.5 Pro Deep
详细介绍我们针对 2.5 Pro Deep Think 的计划
today. Over the past decade, we've laid
。 过去十年，我们
a lot of the foundations for the modern
为现代
AI era. From our pioneering work
人工智能时代奠定了许多基础。 从我们开创性地
inventing the transformers architecture
发明了Transformer架构（
which today underpins all large language
如今它支撑着所有大型语言
models to agent systems like Alph Go and
模型），到像AlphaGo和
Alpha Zero, we continue to double down
Alpha Zero这样的智能体系统，我们不断加倍投入
fundamental research to invent the next
基础研究的广度和深度，以期发明
artificial general intelligence.
人工智能通用所需的下一个重大突破。
Gemini is already the best multimodal
Gemini 已经是最好的多模态
foundation model, but we're working hard
基础模型，但我们正在努力
to extend it to become what we call a
将其扩展为我们所谓的
world model. That is a model that can
世界模型。 这是一个能够像大脑一样，通过模拟世界各个方面来
make plans and imagine new experiences
制定计划和想象新体验的模型
like the brain does. This is something
。
I've always been passionate about,
我一直对虚拟世界充满热情，
since my early days, developing AI for
从我早期开发人工智能用于
simulation games like theme park.
模拟主题公园等游戏开始，我就一直在思考虚拟世界。
direction for a while through our
一段时间以来，我们一直在朝着这个方向努力，从我们
pioneering work training agents to
开创性地训练智能体
master complex games like Go and
掌握围棋和星际争霸等复杂游戏，
Starcraft to most recently our Genie2
到最近推出的 Genie2
model capable of generating 3D simulated
模型，该模型能够生成 3D 模拟
environments that you can interact with
环境，您只需提供
just from a single image
单个图像
prompt. You can already see these
提示即可与之交互。 你已经可以看到这些
capabilities emerging in the way Gemini
能力正在显现，例如 Gemini
can use its world knowledge and
能够运用其世界知识和
reasoning to represent things in nature.
推理能力来表示自然界的事物。
And in VO, our state-of-the-art video
而 VO 是我们最先进的视频
model, which has a deep understanding of
模型，它对直观的物理学有着深刻的理解
intuitive physics, like how gravity,
，例如重力、
light, and materials behave. It's really
光和材料的行为方式。
incredible how well VO maintains
VO在
accuracy and consistency across frames.
各帧画面中保持准确性和一致性的能力真是令人难以置信。
It knows what to do. Even when the
它知道该怎么做。 即使
prompts get a little creative, like this
提示变得有点创意，比如这个
person made out of life
人是用救生筏做成的
rafts, understanding the physical
，了解物理
environment will also be critical for
环境对于
robotics. AI systems will need to need
机器人技术来说也至关重要。 人工智能系统需要
world models to operate effectively in
世界模型才能在现实世界中有效运行
the real world. We fine-tuned a
。 我们对一款名为
specialized model, Gemini Robotics, that
Gemini Robotics 的专用模型进行了微调，该模型可以
teaches robots to do useful things like
教会机器人执行诸如
grasp, follow instructions, and adjust
抓取、遵循指令和
to novel tasks on the fly.
即时适应新任务等有用的任务。
For those of you here today, you can
今天在场的各位，可以
play around with the robots in the AI
在人工智能沙盒里体验一下机器人
sandbox. Making Gemini a full world
。 将 Gemini 打造成一个完整的世界
model is a critical step in unlocking a
模型，是解锁
new kind of AI. One that's helpful in
新型人工智能的关键一步。 一款对
your everyday life, that's intelligent
你的日常生活有帮助、智能
and understands the context you're in,
且能理解你所处环境、
and that can plan and take action on
并且能在任何设备上代表你进行计划和采取行动的应用程序
your behalf across any device. This is
。 这就是
our ultimate vision for the Gemini app
我们对 Gemini 应用的最终愿景，
to transform it into a universal AI
将其转变为一款通用人工智能
assistant. An AI that's personal,
助手。 一款个性化、
proactive, and powerful. And one of our
主动且强大的AI。 这是我们
key milestones on the road to
迈向通用人工智能道路上的关键里程碑之一
AGI. This starts with the capabilities
。 这首先要从
we first explored last year in Project
我们去年在 Astra 项目中首次探索的功能入手
Astra, such as video understanding,
，例如视频理解、
screen sharing, and memory. Over the
屏幕共享和内存。 过去
past year, we've been integrating
一年，我们一直在将这些
capabilities like these into Gemini Live
功能集成到 Gemini Live 中，
for more people to experience
以便更多人今天就能体验到这些功能
today. Of course, we continue to
。 当然，我们将继续
relentlessly improve and explore new
不懈努力，不断改进，探索
frontier. For example, we've upgraded
前沿领域的新创新。 例如，我们升级了
voice output to be more natural with
语音输出，使其更加自然，采用
native audio. We've improved memory and
原生音频。 我们改进了内存并
added computer control. Let's take a
增加了计算机控制功能。 我们
look. I'm here with the latest research
来看一下。 我带着
prototype of Project Astra, and we're
阿斯特拉计划的最新研究原型机来了，我们
going to see how it can help me fix my
来看看它能否帮我修好
bike.
自行车。
Hey, go online and look for a user's
嘿，上网找找
manual for a Huffy mountain bike.
Huffy 山地自行车的用户手册。
I have found a user manual for you. What
我找到了一份用户手册。
would you like to know about it? Okay,
你想了解这方面的什么信息？ 好的，
cool. Now, scroll until you find the
明白了。 现在，向下滚动直到找到
section about the brakes. Sure thing.
有关刹车的部分。 当然可以。
Looking for that page now. I think I
正在查找该页面。 我觉得我把
stripped the screw. Can you go on
螺丝拧花了。 你能去
YouTube and find a video for how to fix
YouTube 上找找看有没有相关的视频教你怎么解决
that? Of course. I'm opening YouTube
这个问题吗？ 当然。 我现在打开YouTube
now.
。
This looks like a good video. Place a
这看起来是个不错的视频。 将
rubber band over the head of the screw
橡皮筋套在螺丝头上，
and press down firmly. Can you go
然后用力向下按压。 你能帮我查看一下
through my emails with the bike shop and
我和自行车店的邮件往来，
find which size hex nut I need? Sure.
找出我需要的六角螺母的尺寸吗？ 当然。
According to the email from Bicycle
根据 Bicycle
Habitat, you need a 3/8 in hex nut for
Habitat 的电子邮件，你的链轮需要一个 3/8 英寸的六角螺母
your sprocket. I've highlighted the
。 我已经帮
correct bin for you. It seems like I
你标出了正确的垃圾桶。 我好像
need a spare tension screw. Can you call
需要一个备用的张紧螺丝。 您能打电话给
the nearest bike shop and see what they
最近的自行车店问问他们
have in stock? Yep. Calling them now.
有什么库存吗？ 是的。 现在就给他们打电话。
I'll get back to you with what they have
我会尽快回复你他们的
in stock. I think my brake pads are
库存情况。 我觉得我的刹车片
wearing down. Can you check the manual
磨损快了。 请您再查阅一下手册，
again and see if it talks about them
看看里面有没有提到这些内容
anywhere? According to the manual, if
？ 根据手册，请
you look on page 24, do you want to get
翻到第 24 页，您想吃
lunch? Yeah. Give me 5 minutes. Can you
午饭吗？ 是的。 给我五分钟时间。 你能把刚才
finish what you were saying? As I was
说的话说完吗？ 正如我刚才
saying, if you look on page 24, section
所说，如果你查看第 24 页
two, you'll see how to replace the brake
第二部分，你就会看到如何更换刹车
pads. Hey, uh, any updates on that call?
片。 嘿，呃，那通电话有什么最新进展吗？   是的
Yep. I just got off of the bike shop.
。 我刚从自行车店出来。
They confirm they have your tension
他们确认他们有您需要的张力
screw in stock. Would you like me to
螺丝库存。 您想让我帮您下单自取吗
place a pickup order? Could you show me
？ 你能给我展示
some examples of dog baskets I could put
一些可以装在自行车上的狗篮的例子吗
on my bike? Sure, I can help you with
？ 当然，我可以帮你
that. Just give me a moment.
。 请稍等片刻。
Here are some options. I think Zuka
以下是一些选择。 我觉得祖卡穿
these. A universal AI assistant will
这身[音乐]肯定很好看。 通用人工智能助手将为
perform everyday tasks for us. It'll
我们执行日常任务。 它将
take care of mundane admin and surface
处理繁琐的行政事务，并提供令人
delightful new recommendations, making
愉悦的新推荐，从而
us more productive and enriching our
提高我们的工作效率，丰富我们的
lives. We're gathering feedback about
生活。 我们正在
these new capabilities now from trusted
从值得信赖的测试人员那里收集有关这些新功能的反馈，
testers and working to bring them to
并努力将它们引入
Gemini Live, new experiences in search
Gemini Live，
and the live API for developers, as well
为开发者带来全新的搜索体验和实时 API，
as new form factors like Android XR
以及 Android XR 眼镜等新外形
glasses. You'll hear more on this later
。 今天晚些时候你会听到更多相关消息
today.
。
My entire career at its core has been
我的整个职业生涯的核心都是
about using AI to advance knowledge and
利用人工智能来增进知识和
accelerate scientific discovery. At
加速科学发现。 在
Google DeepMind, we've been applying AI
谷歌DeepMind，我们长期以来一直在
across almost every branch of science
几乎所有科学领域应用人工智能
for a long time. In just the past year,
。 仅在过去一年里，
we've made some huge breakthroughs in a
我们在
wide range of areas from mathematics to
从数学到
life
生命
sciences. We've built Alpha Proof that
科学等众多领域都取得了巨大的突破。 我们打造了 Alpha Proof，它
can solve mass Olympia problems at the
能够解决奥运会银牌级别的大规模比赛难题
silver medal level. co-scientist that
。
can collaborate with researchers,
能够与研究人员合作，
helping them develop and test novel
帮助他们提出和检验新
hypotheses. And we've just released
假设的合作科学家。 我们刚刚发布了
Alpha Evolve, which can discover new
Alpha Evolve，它可以发现新的
scientific knowledge and speed up AI
科学知识并加快人工智能
itself. In the life sciences, we've
自身的训练速度。 在生命科学领域，我们
built Amy, a research system that could
开发了 Amy，这是一个可以
help clinicians with medical diagnosis.
帮助临床医生进行医学诊断的研究系统。
Alphold 3, which can predict the
Alphold 3 可以预测
structure and interactions of all of
所有脂质分子的结构和相互作用
lice molecules, and Isomorphic Labs,
，而 Isomorphic Labs 则
which builds on our Alphafold work to
基于我们的 Alphafold 工作，
discovery process with AI and will one
利用人工智能彻底改变药物发现过程，并有朝一日将
day help to solve many global
帮助解决许多全球
diseases. In just a few short years,
性疾病。 短短几年内，
Alphafold has already had a massive
Alphafold 已经
impact in the scientific community. It's
对科学界产生了巨大的影响。 它已
become a standard tool for biology and
成为生物学和
medical research with over 2.5 million
医学研究的标准工具，全球有超过 250 万
researchers worldwide using in their
研究人员在其
critical
重要
work. As we continue to make progress
工作中使用它。 随着我们不断
towards AGI, I've always believed if
向通用人工智能（AGI）迈进，我始终相信，如果以
done safely and responsibly, it has the
安全负责的方式进行，它有
potential to accelerate scientific
可能加速科学
discovery and be the most beneficial
发现，并成为有史以来最有益的
technology ever invented.
技术。
Taking a step back, it's amazing to me
回过头来看，令我惊叹的是，
that even just a few years ago, the
就在几年前，
frontier technology you're seeing today
你今天看到的这些前沿技术在我
would have seemed nothing short of
看来简直就是
magic. It's exciting to see these
魔法。 令人兴奋的是，这些
technologies powering new experiences in
技术正在为
products like search and Gemini and also
搜索和 Gemini 等产品带来全新体验，并且
coming together to help people in their
能够共同帮助人们改善
daily lives. For example, we recently
日常生活。 例如，我们最近
partnered with IRA, a company that
与 IRA 建立了合作关系，该公司
by connecting them via video to human
通过视频将盲人和低视力人士与人类
visual
视觉
interpreters. Using Astra technology, we
翻译员联系起来，帮助他们更好地融入世界。 利用 Astra 技术，我们
build a prototype to help more people
构建了一个原型，以帮助更多的人
have access to this type of
获得此类
assistance. We're getting ongoing
援助。 我们正在不断收集
feedback from users while Iris
用户的反馈，同时 Iris
interpreters are actively supervising
翻译人员也在积极监督，
for safety and reliability.
以确保安全性和可靠性。
With this and all our groundbreaking
凭借这项技术以及我们所有突破性的
work, we're building AI that's more
工作，我们正在构建更加
personal, proactive, and powerful,
个性化、更积极主动、更强大的AI，从而
enriching our lives, advancing the pace
丰富我们的生活，加快
of scientific progress, and ushering in
科学进步的步伐，并开启
a new golden age of discovery and
一个充满发现和奇迹的新黄金时代
wonder.
。
Please read
请阅读
Patel. Search the mode.
帕特尔的文章。 搜索模式。
Gentle monster
温柔的怪物
packer. Gentle monster.
打包者。 温柔的怪物。
for Apple intelligence.
为了苹果公司的智能技术。